<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<book>
         <tag>Welcome to our Tour and Travel website, where you can explore the most fascinating destinations across the
          globe. We offer a range of travel options to suit your interests, budget, and preferences. Here is a brief
          overview of our services:</tag>

        <p class="service-detail"><b>Tour Packages:</b> Our tour packages are designed to take you to the best
          destinations around the world, whether you want to experience the culture, history, wildlife, or natural
          beauty of a place. We offer customized packages for solo travelers, couples, families, and groups.</p>

        <p class="service-detail"><b> Flights: </b>We provide flight bookings to any destination worldwide, with
          competitive pricing and top-notch service. Our team of travel experts can help you find the best flight deals
          and provide you with personalized recommendations.</p>

        <p class="service-detail"> <b>Hotels:</b> We offer a wide range of hotels, from budget-friendly options to
          luxury resorts. Our team ensures that you get the best rates, convenient locations, and high-quality service
          during your stay.</p>

        <p class="service-detail"> <b>Activities: </b> We offer a variety of activities to suit all interests, whether
          you want to go on a safari, hike in the mountains, or explore a new city. Our team can help you plan and book
          your activities, ensuring that you have an unforgettable experience.</p>

        <p class="service-detail"> <b> Transportation:</b> We provide transportation services, including car rentals and
          airport transfers, to make your travel experience hassle-free and convenient.</p>

        <p class="service-detail"> <b>Travel Insurance:</b> We offer travel insurance to ensure that you are covered in
          case of any unforeseen circumstances during your trip.</p>
        <p> At our Tour and Travel website, we are committed to providing you with the best travel experience possible.
          Our team of experienced travel experts is dedicated to making your journey seamless, comfortable, and
          enjoyable. So, whether you are planning a romantic getaway, family vacation, or solo adventure, we have got
          you covered.</p>
</book>